Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nnamdialozie (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Management Consulting Financial Analysis Project Management

Nnamdi Alozie

Executive | Healthcare Strategy | Innovation | Advisor Cambridge, Massachusetts, United States

Summary

Healthcare and management executive with over 15 years experience in strategy, operations, and Innovation. Committed to building a healthier, equitable and efficient healthcare system.

Specialties: Innovation Strategy, Strategic Planning, Operations, Project Management, Business Process Redesign, Healthcare, Managed Care, Population Health Management, Care Management, Medical Cost & Utilization Management, Home Healthcare, Market Analysis, Financial Analysis, Financial modeling, Business Case Development, Competitive Analysis, Home Care.

Experience

Beth Israel Lahey Health Vice President, Strategy and Business Development June 2022 - Present (11 months)

aptihealth Investor February 2022 - Present (1 year 3 months)

CogniFit
Advisory Board Member
December 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months)

CogniFit is a digital healthcare company focused on assessing and improving cognitive health.

More than 4 million people use our digital products, which are available in 19 languages. We work with companies, hospitals, universities, foundations, and research centers around the world to offer the best digital cognitive assessment and trainings in the world. CogniFit is a market leader in the braintraining wellness area, and runs intensive clinical research to validate the next

generation of digital-therapeutics brain-conditions such as cognitive treatment for Depression, Insomnia, Chemo Brain, Epilepsy and more.

What If Ventures

Investor

June 2020 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Investor in mental health and addiction-focused startups

The Coneflower Institute Advisory Board Member August 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months)

At The Coneflower Institute, we are passionate about ending the social stigma surrounding Mental Health Conditions. Through education, advocacy, and research, we seek to support the Mental Health Ecosystem.

Liberty Grove Schools **Board Member** January 2021 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Indiana University Health Director, Corporate Strategy 2018 - May 2022 (4 years)

EXL

Assistant Vice President (Engagement Manager) 2016 - 2017 (1 year)

Greater Chicago Area | NYC

crankfrog (The Chartis group) Senior Consultant, Healthcare Strategy 2014 - 2015 (1 year)

Washington D.C. Metro Area

Northwestern University - Kellogg School of Management Full-time Student 2012 - 2014 (2 years) Greater Chicago Area

Sam's Club

Strategy and Business Development Intern, Health and Wellness June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

VNSNY

Sr. Associate, Quality Management & Analytics 2004 - 2012 (8 years)

New York, NY

Awazoo.com Founder 2001 - 2003 (2 years)

Education

Northwestern University - Kellogg School of Management Master of Business Administration (M.B.A), Innovation, Management & Strategy

New York University

City University of New York

Harvard Business School Executive Course · (2019 - 2019)